Fred A. Riecker Papers 1848-1967 (bulk 1930-1967)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Fred A. Riecker Papers 1848-1967 (bulk 1930-1967)
MS 493
Riecker, Fred A.
The Fred A. Riecker Papers includes correspondence, legal documents, ledgers, real estate abstracts, photographic prints, negatives, maps, charts, railroad tickets and itineraries, dated 1858-1967 (bulk 1930-1967) pertaining to Fred A. Riecker and the Riecker family. The bulk of the material consists of legal and financial documents that relate to the parcel of real estate, otherwise known as Riecker’s Addition, as well as Fred A. Riecker’s professional career as a railroad surveying engineer and civil advocate for Tucson.
5.5 linear ft.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Biographical Note
Fred A. Riecker was born in San Francisco, California, 1878, but shortly thereafter moved with his mother to Tucson, Arizona. He later began his professional career as a railroad survey engineer during the early 20th century for various locomotive companies throughout the American Southwest. In subsequent years, he worked as a civil engineer in Tucson. Throughout his life, he was intellectually engaged in a number of civil issues concerning Tucson and the greater Southwest that prompted his extensive writing of letters to various newspaper editors and politicians. In his later years, Fred A. Riecker published a semi-autobiographical manuscript detailing the pre- and post-railroad Tucson pioneer life of his family in “Horatio Algebra and Chief One and One.”
His father, Paul Riecker, was a nationally renown civil and mining engineer who drew the first official map of the Arizona territory which was published in 1879 from his previous topographical survey of California and Arizona as part of the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers. He led an early exploration party across the Colorado Plateau and was among the first to make contact with the Havasupai at the Grand Canyon. Paul Riecker sued for homestead rights, thereby creating the origins of Riecker’s Addition. He built the first houses north of the railroad tracks in Tucson in 1880. In 1896, Paul Riecker mapped Pasadena, California, and laid out Inglewood and Redondo Beach, California. He was also involved in the Panama-Nicaragua Canal controversy as one of the original surveyors of the Nicaragua Canal route.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series, each containing a variety of subseries.
Series I: Fred A. Riecker, 1878-1967
Subseries I: Correspondence, 1908-1967
Subseries II: Personal, 1898-1967
Subseries III: Professional, 1894-1957
Subseries IV: "Horatio Algebra and Chief One and One", 1957-1961
Subseries V: Water Reclamation, 1931-1967
Subseries VI: Newspaper Clippings, 1934-1964
Subseries VII: Financial, 1938-1967
Subseries VIII: Journals, 1905-1967
Subseries IX: Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1950-1957
Subseries X: Checks and check stubs, 1940-1967
Series II: Riecker Family, 1858-1967
Subseries I: Correspondence, 1868-1963
Subseries II: Family Documents, 1848-1963
Subseries III: Financial, 1920-1945
Subseries IV: Newspaper Clippings, 1887-1967
Subseries V: Riecker's Addition, 1882-1962
Series III: Photographs and A/V Media, 1878-1967
Subseries I: Portraits, 1878-1936
Subseries II: Fred A. Riecker, circa 1910-1965
Subseries III: Negatives, 1964
Subseries IV: Audio Recordings, 1959-1963
Scope and Content Note
The Fred A. Riecker Papers includes correspondence, legal documents, ledgers, real estate abstracts, photographic prints, negatives, maps, charts, railroad tickets and itineraries, dated 1858-1967 (bulk 1930-1967) pertaining to Fred A. Riecker and the Riecker family. The bulk of the material consists of legal and financial documents that relate to the parcel of real estate, otherwise known as Riecker’s Addition, as well as Fred A. Riecker’s professional career as a railroad surveying engineer and civil advocate for Tucson.
Other material in the collection is composed of correspondence belonging to various Riecker family members that invoke a variety of subjects such as real estate, family estates and financial investments. Many of the correspondences are between Fred A. Riecker and his family members, but others include letters to politicians, newspaper editors and personal contacts. The Fred A. Riecker Papers also include a number of photographic portraits taken of individual members of the Riecker family and photographic prints of Tucson landmarks and the University of Arizona. Finally, there are several maps and charts created and used both by Fred and Paul Riecker during their respective professional tenure as civil engineers.
Access Terms
Riecker, Fred A., 1878-1967
Riecker, Paul
University of Arizona
History -- Tucson (Ariz.)
Pioneers -- Tucson (Ariz.)
Civil engineers -- Tucson (Ariz.)
Riecker's Addition -- Tucson (Ariz.)
Railroads -- Tucson (Ariz.)
Photography -- Tucson (Ariz.)
Correspondence
Financial records
Maps
Container List
- Series I: Fred A. Riecker 1878-1967
  - Subseries I: Correspondence, 1908-1967
    Fred A. Riecker’s correspondences are arranged chronologically. The subseries contains letters relating to his professional career as a railroad-surveying engineer, letters to editors and officials, and personal correspondence between family members and friends.
    - Marie Randall, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Professional, 1910-1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1919-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Annie W. Riecker, 1920-1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Tucson Air Service, 1927-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Colorado River Project, 1930-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Medical, 1932-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Letters to the editor, 1932-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Letters to the editor, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Letters to government officials, 1932-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Edna F. Riecker [Sister Mary Winifred], 1938-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Ruth Slattery, 1938-1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Postcards with photographic background, 1939-1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Eugene Riecker, 1941-1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Arizona Pioneer's Historical Society and the National Geographic Society, 1942-1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Myrtle Riecker, 1945-1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Myrtle Riecker, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Belden Family, 1948-1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Charitable Causes, 1950-1962 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Evelyn Bernstein, 1950-1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Rena Pendleton, 1952-1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Hazel Kempf, 1952-1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Sarah McKenna, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Frank Squire, 1956-1966 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Gladys Stanton, 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Relating to the Caryl Chessman case, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - "Horatio Algebra and Chief One and One", 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - East Broadway subway, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - United Nations relocation, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Dr. John and Alice Ruddock, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Proposals for new counties in Arizona, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Greeting cards, 1937-1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Greeting cards, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Envelopes, 1937-1964 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Subseries II: Personal, 1894-1967
    The personal documents belonging to Fred A. Riecker are arranged chronologically. The subseries contains documents relevant to Fred A. Riecker’s personal life, such as documents reflecting his matriculation and medical records, as well as documents relating to his estate and personal travels.
    - Higher education documents, 1894-1901 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - General documents, 1918-1966 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Automobile documents, 1919-1961 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Medical documents, 1932-1967 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Europe trip memorabilia, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Europe trip memorabilia>, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Europe trip memorabilia>, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Notes and jottings, 1954-1958 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Notes and jottings, 1959-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Notes and jottings, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Funeral and estate documents, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Subseries III: Professional, 1894-1957
    The professional documents belonging to Fred A. Riecker are arranged chronologically. The subseries contains documents that shed light on Fred A. Riecker’s career as a survey and civil engineer for various railroad companies, as well as maps and charts employed by both Paul and Fred Riecker during their work.
    - Railroad papers, 1894-1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen documents, 1898-1900 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Southern Pacific Railroad Company documents, 1907-1917 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Charts, diagrams and tables, 1914-1920 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Published documents, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe / Union Pacific Railroad proposed route, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Holy Hope Cemetary, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Map: Feather River 650 ft. dam, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Map: Southern Pacific Lands Company, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Subseries IV: "Horatio Algebra and Chief One and One", 1957-1961
    The manuscripts and documents relating to Fred A. Riecker's published work, "Horatio Algebra and Chief One and One", are arranged chronologically. The subseries contains documents involving Fred A. Riecker's research and subsequent publishing of his book. The written work was made as an attempt to document the Riecker family’s early Tucson pioneer life.
    - Notes and jottings, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Pencil manuscripts, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Early notes and drafts, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Typescripts, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Copyright documents, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - First typed copy, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Salt River Project, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Subseries V: Water Reclamation 1931-1967
    The documents that deal with water reclamation rights are arranged chronologically. The subseries has documents addressing the water reclamation issues that Fred A. Riecker advocated for on Tucson’s behalf.
    - Information pamphlets, 1930-1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - "Suspended Sediment and Chemical Analyses of San Pedro River at Charleston, Arizona.", 1961 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Colorado River Project notes, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Central Valley Project, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Subseries VI: Newspaper Clippings 1934-1964
    The newspaper clippings are arranged chronologically and separated by two of the most occurring types of newspaper clippings Fred A. Riecker collected throughout his life. “Arizona Album” was printed in the newspaper featuring early Arizona pioneering families.
    - General, 1934-1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - "Arizona Album", 1958-1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Subseries VII: Financial, 1938-1967
    The financial documents and records are arranged chronologically. The subseries contains documents pertaining to Fred A. Riecker’s financial and real estate assets.
    - Investments and securities documents, 1938-1958 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Insurance documents, 1945-1956 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - State and County Tax Receipts, 1950-1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Statements of account [Union Bank], 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Statements of account [Southern Arizona Bank and First Western Bank], 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Subseries VIII: Journals, 1905-1967
    The journals, diaries and ledgers are arranged chronologically. The subseries contains journals, diaries and ledgers Fred A. Riecker maintained throughout his professional and personal life.
    - Journal -- Field Book, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Journal -- Field Book, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Journal -- Notebook, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Ledger [No.1], 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Ledger [No.2], 1935 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Ledger [No.3], 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Ledger [No.4], 1936 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Ledger [No.5], 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Journal -- Weekly Calendar, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Ledger -- Order Book, 1939-1953 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Ledger -- Order Book, 1944-1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Journal -- Weekly Calendar, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Ledger -- Xerox Copy, 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Journal -- Personal Diary, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Journal -- Notebook, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Subseries IX: Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1950-1957
    The railroad tickets and itineraries of Fred A. Riecker from 1950-1957 are arranged chronologically. The tickets and itineraries from distinct railroad companies display images and advertising indicative of the 1950s and 1960s.
    - Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Railroad Tickets and Itineraries, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Subseries X: Checks and Check stubs, 1940-1967
    The checks and check stubs of several dozen individual checks and check stubs belonging to Fred A. Riecker are arranged in chronological order.
    - Checks and check stubs, 1940-1967 (Box 7)
- Series II: Riecker Family 1848-1967
  - Subseries I: Correspondence, 1868-1963
    The correspondence is arranged chronologically and organized by topic. The subseries contains letters and documents covering a number of financial, civil and familial topics, such as Riecker’s Addition and the estate of various Riecker family members.
    - Paul Riecker [German], 1868-1870 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - California real estate, 1913-1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Riecker's Addition, 1914-1932 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Riecker's Addition, 1941-1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Riecker's Addition, 1951-1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Riecker's Addition -- Office of the County Treasurer, 1918-1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Stocks and shares, 1914-1932 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Tax and Treasury Departments, 1929-1932 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Between family members, 1929-1939 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Between family members, 1943-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Annie W. Riecker's estate, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Annie W. Riecker's estate, 1938-1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Edna F. Riecker's estate, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Annie W. Riecker's Memorial Lecture Series, 1955-1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Subseries II: Family documents, 1848-1963
    The documents belonging to the Riecker family are arranged chronologically. The subseries contains documents corresponding to the Riecker family and estate, including Paul Riecker’s map created for the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers and birth and baptism certificates belonging to various Riecker family members.
    - Birth and baptism certificates, 1848-1928 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Riecker's Addition real estate, 1882-1938 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Lilian E. Austin's estate, 1912-1913 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - California real estate, 1923, 1935-1942, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Annie W. Riecker's estate, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Annie W. Riecker's estate, 1938-1941 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Edna F. Riecker's [Sister Mary Winifred] estate, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Edna F. Riecker's [Sister Mary Winifred] estate, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Myrtle Riecker's estate, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Inglewood, California cemetery family plot, 1913-1918 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Edna F. Riecker's [Sister Mary Winifred] U.S.C. commencement week booklets, 1924-1929 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Edna F. Riecker's [Sister Mary Winifred] U.S.C. diploma of graduation, 1924-1929 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Edna F. Riecker's [Sister Mary Winifred] higher education records, 1924-1929 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Annie W. Riecker's Memorial Lecture Series No.2 and No.4, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Map: Paul Riecker -- Atlas Sheet No.10, 1877 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Subseries III: Financial, 1920-1945
    The financial documents and records relevant to the Riecker family are arranged chronologically and by document type. The subseries contain financial records related to the Riecker family as well as income tax and investment documents from various Riecker family members.
    - Annie W. Riecker's insurance and statement of accounts, 1920-1932 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Stocks and shares notes, 1927-1967 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Annie W. Riecker's federal income tax returns, 1928-1933 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Insurance and real estate documents, 1929-1936 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Edna F. Riecker's [Sister Mary Winifred] individual income tax returns, 1938-1945 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Subseries IV: Newspaper clippings, 1887-1967
    The newspaper clippings are arranged chronologically. The subseries contain published newspaper articles concerning the Riecker family and Riecker’s Addition.
    - General, 1887-1967 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Riecker's Addition, 1922-1931 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Annie W. Riecker's Memorial Lecture Series, 1960-1967 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Subseries V: Riecker's Addition, 1882-1962
    The documents and records relating to the Riecker’s Addition are arranged chronologically and by document type. The subseries contains documents and records relating to Riecker’s Addition, such as abstracts, indentures, tax receipts, and assessment notes about the real estate property.
    - Abstracts copied from Pima County Recorder's Office, 1882-1920 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Indentures, abstracts and bargain sale deeds, 1890-1912 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Indentures, abstracts and bargain sale deeds, 1913-1928 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - State, County and City taxes, 1891-1924 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - State, County and City taxes, 1925-1932 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - State, County and City taxes, 1933-1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Drafts of letters and proposals relating to the City Assessments of Street Improvements, 1916-1929 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Drafts of letters and proposals relating to the City Assessments of Street Improvements, 1930-1938 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Notes copied from the U.S. General Surveyor General's Office, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Sketches, maps and survey notes, 1919-1930 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - City Assessments of Street Improvements, 1919-1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Property assessment documents, 1920-1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Property assessment notes, 1928-1931 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Contracts for sale of real estate property, 1929-1943 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - City of Tucson Resolutions [1181, 1225, 1230], 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - City Assessments of Street Improvements notes, 1939-1943 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Map: Survey by G. J. Roskruge -- Riecker's Addition to Tucson, circa 1890 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Map: Survey by G.J. Roskruge -- Riecker's Addition to Tucson, circa 1890 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Map: Riecker's Addition to Tucson, circa 1900 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Blueprint: Plat of Riecker's Addition, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Map: USGS, California and Arizona, circa 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Map: Tucson, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Map: Carbon print of Riecker's Addition -- Large, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Map: Carbon print of Riecker's Addition -- Small, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Series III: Photographs and Audio/ Visual Media 1878-1967
  - Subseries I: Portraits, 1878-1936
    The portraits are arranged chronologically and arranged by individual. The subseries contains a painted portrait of the Riecker children and various individual and group portraits of the Riecker family.
    - Fred A. Riecker, 1878-1936 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Group portraits, 1885-1928 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Annie W. Riecker, 1889-1934 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Eugene Riecker, circa 1910 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Edna F. Riecker [Sister Mary Winifred], circa 1920 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Annie W. Riecker Memorial Lecture Series, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Family album, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Riecker extended family, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Painted portrait of Riecker children, 1883 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Subseries II: Fred A. Riecker, circa 1910-1965
    The photographs of Fred A. Riecker are arranged chronologically and by subject type. The subseries contains a collection of photographs Fred A. Riecker made throughout his life.
    - Railroad engineer, circa 1910 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - S.S. Manhattan, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Downtown Tucson, 1957-1967 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Greater Tucson, 1957-1964 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - University of Arizona, 1964-1964 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "Water for nature's storehouse -- the forest; Apache.", 1931 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "Roads are the arteries of the forest; Apache.", 1931 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "National forest timber is harvested on a sustained yield basis; Sitgraves.", 1931 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "Head of cattle graze the national forest ranges of Arizona in 1931; Sitgraves." (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Subseries III: Negatives, 1964
    The negatives in this subseries are of some of the photographs located in the Photographic and A/V series.
    - Negatives, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Subseries IV: Audio Recording Tapes, 1959-1963
    The audio recording tapes of Fred A. Riecker reading from his book, “Horatio Algebra and Chief One and One” are arranged in chronological order.
    - Audio recording tape, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Audio recording tape, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Audio recording tape, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)